DAYNA JON QUILLIN

2006 Balsam Way, Round Rock, TX 78665 • M80.daynajq@gmail.com • (512) 803-7456

OBJECTIVES

With over 16 years of outstanding customer service and satisfaction, advocating equanimity and dignity while promoting conscientiousness and ethics through character cultivation are my personal policies. These personal policies facilitate fundamental connections with the folks involved in all my endeavors. All of my clients and coworkers after working with me can attest that they are not just a number, but an invaluable asset. Unfortunately, due to an accident, I am unable to continue my career in Emergency Medical Services. Fortunately I am still able to continue to do what I love, bringing positivity into people's lives!

EDUCATION

EMTS Academy

November 2015 • Emergency Medical Technician – B

2011 Austin Community College Majors: Business, Anthropology

CERTIFICATIONS & SKILLS

American Sign Language (ASL) * Intermediate level of communication & interpreting

TABC Certification • July 2019

Advanced Life Support * October 2017

CPR & AED • July 2019

FEMA *October 2015

Introduction to Hazardous Materials * Emergency Management Institute

OSHA Safety in the Workplace Compliance • 2015

HIPPA and Patient Confidentiality * 2015

NREMT *December 2015 Registry #: E3225836

EMT – B Certification November 2015 EMTS Academy

REFERENCES

Sean Mullin * Former Supervisor * (512) 658-2948 * seanmullin@me.com

Seth Spurgers * Former Supervisor * (512) 263-0700 * sspurgers@goldsgym.com

Corey Savala * Former Supervisor * csavala@goldsgym.com

Dorsie Martin * Former Coworker * (512) 284-5847

EXPERIENCE

Favor Deliveries • 1705 Guadalupe St, Austin, TX Runner • June 2017 – Currently an independent contractor

Uncle Gary's Bar • Farm to Market Road Pflugerville, TX Bartender • June 2019 – Currently Employed

Acadian Ambulance • 4100 E. Ed Bluestein Blvd. Austin, TX EMT-B • October 2017 – March 2018

Golds Gym • 12480 Bee Cave Rd, Bee Cave, TX Housekeeping; Kid's Club • June 2015 – February 2017

The Great Vapor Caper • 1807 Red Fox Rd.
Owner & CEO • June 2012 – January 2016

Target * 2300 W Ben White Blvd, Austin, TX Logistics Early AM; Instocks; Team lead/Manager * October 2011 – May 2012

Black Sheep Lodge * 2108 S Lamar Blvd, Austin, TX Waitress; Bartender * July 2010 – February 2011

Cherry Creek Catfish * 5712 Manchaca Rd, Austin, TX Manager; Waitress, Bartender, Hostess, Line Cook * December 2008 – July 2010

> Chilis • Buda, TX & Austin, TX Waitress • November 2005 – November 2009

Thank you so much for your time reviewing my resume!

I sincerely hope my words have sparked your interest and look forward to our future pursuits!

Have a great and productive day!